米奇尔 我是克莱尔 现在是周六早上
Hey, Mitchell. Claire. Saturday morning.
我要你去给妈妈买一份生日礼物
Look, I need you to buy Mom a birthday present
然后说是我们俩合送的
and say it's from the both of us.
就这样 谢谢 拜拜
Okay, thanks. Bye-bye --
我知道这不是语音留言
No, I know it's not a voicemail.
我只是不想听你唧唧歪歪
I just don't want to hear you whine about it.
不行 不行 那些是给艾丽克斯的
No, no, no, those are for Alex.
我今天要送去宿舍给她
I'm taking them up to her dorm today.
你也知道她最近压力多大
You know how stressed she gets.
我想她能随时得到来自母亲的安慰
She can always use a little comfort from her loving mom.
为什么艾丽克斯有爱心包裹 而我却没有
Why does Alex get a care package and not me?
你就住在爱心包裹里
You live in a care package.
海莉 赶紧把人皮画上 到楼上来
Haley, put your face on and get up here!
我们上班要迟到了
We're gonna be late for work!
我最近在存钱给自己买公寓
I'm saving up to get my own apartment,
所以我和卢克一起在俱乐部打工
so I've been working at the club with Luke.
是给卢克打工
For Luke.
这妹子是我手下最赞的球车女郎
Kid's my best cart girl.
我给高尔夫球手送饮料
I deliver drinks to golfers.
小费挺可观 不过 我花了几天
Tips are good, but, uh... it took me a couple days
才领会了这比赛的细枝末节
to learn the finer points of the game.
要鸡尾酒吗 帅哥们
Cocktails, boys?
在你左手边
On your left.
那是艾丽克斯的旧单车吗
Is that Alex's old bike?
是的 重新组装的
Yes, totally rebuilt.
只花了我三个月时间和两管破伤风针
It only took me three months and two tetanus shots.
她最近一直暗示想要辆车
She's been dropping hints about wanting some wheels.
你确定她说的不是...
Are you sure she didn't mean a --
独轮车吗 不 她肯定说了"多轮"车
Unicycle? No. She definitely said "wheels."
车篮正好用来放盥洗用品
Well, the basket's perfect for loading up the toiletries.
还记得我们上次去那里吗
Remember last time we went up there?
她正在用女厕的肥皂粉洗头
She was washing her hair with the powdered soap from the ladies room.
艾丽克斯是个聪明 有学问的...
Alex is an intelligent, accomplished --
-你就直说了吧 -马大哈
- You can just say it. ?- Scatterbrain.
她有时太用功念书
Sometimes, she studies so hard
会忘记一些小事
she forgets about the little things.
我去图书馆
I'll be at the library.
女儿 你是不是忘了什么东西
Uh, honey...aren't you forgetting something?
差点忘了
That was close.
老天
God.
我去处理
I'm on it.
这里就是未来四年我称为"家"的地方
So, this is the place I'll call home for the next four years.
而且因为你念的是戏剧系
And because you're a theater major,
这很可能是你这辈子最大的公寓了
probably the biggest apartment you'll ever have.
在开学第一天 我不想发生两件事
There are two things I want to avoid my first day of school:
被发现我洗完澡穿着滑水鞋出来
getting caught leaving the shower in my aqua shoes,
以及挥泪告别
and a tearful goodbye.
我的同学们始终会看到我哭
My classmates are gonna see me cry eventually.
但我希望是在谢幕的那一刻看见
I'd prefer it be during a curtain call.
我是哥伦比亚人
I am Colombian,
满足曼尼的愿望有违我的天性
so it's against my nature to give Manny what he wants:
他想要冷漠的白人式告别
a cold, white-people goodbye.
但我知道他很多愁善感
But I know he's sensitive,
离家让他很难过
and he's having a hard time leaving the nest,
所以我会顺他的意
so I'm gonna give it to him.
祝你好运 室友
Good luck, chum.
你的浓缩咖啡机想放在哪里
Where do you want your espresso machine?
放我书桌上就行
On my desk is fine.
别担心 特雷弗
And don't worry, Trevor.
买咖啡豆的钱用脏话罐里的罚款付
We'll pay for the beans with the money from our swear jar.
别忘了 四点后不许喝咖啡
Don't forget -- no coffee after 4:00,
否则你会做噩梦
or you get the nightmares.
接下来我自己搞定就行了
I think I can take it from here.
谢谢二位的帮忙
Thank you both for all of your help.
不客气
Sure thing.
我们保持联络 儿子
We will keep in touch, son.
这位朋友
Well, my friend,
你刚刚见证了十分罕见的完美告别
you have just witnessed the rare perfect goodbye.
历史上仅记录到过几次完美告别
History records but few flawless farewells:
奥斯卡·王尔德临终之时的珠玑妙语
Oscar Wilde's deathbed bon mot,
白瑞德毫不在乎...
Rhett Butler not giving a --
我靠
Damn it.
我把白噪音机忘在家了
I left my white noise machine at home.
这下我不得不回去
Now I have to go back there,
可能会毁掉我们的完美告别呢
and risk ruining our perfect goodbye.
但你会感谢我的 特雷弗
But you're gonna thank me, Trevor.
持续的背景噪音能安抚...
There's something soothing about constant background noise that...
小特
Trev?
一杯金汤力
One gin and tonic.
希望不是你... 开车[开球]
I hope you're not... driving.
抱歉 这笑话通常高尔夫球手们都很喜欢
Sorry, that's usually a big hit with the golfers.
很好笑
It was hilarious.
但我尽力避免长出笑纹
But I'm trying to avoid laugh lines.
我懂
I get that.
我不想长鱼尾纹 所以我从不眯眼
I don't want crow's feet, so I never squint,
哪怕警察正用手电筒直照我的双眼
even if a cop is shining his flashlight directly in my eyes.
我每周一次穿着涂满凡士林的潜水服睡觉
Once a week, I sleep in a wetsuit full of Vaseline.
效果显著啊
It shows.
简直像遇到三十年后的我
It was like meeting myself in 30 years.
原来我真的驻颜有术
Turns out, I really held up.
早上好 拉帕波特女士
Good morning, Ms. Rappaport.
你好
Oh, hello...
-你叫杜克对吧 -是的
- Duke, is it? ?- Yes.
海莉 你是不是该回球车上去了
Haley, shouldn't you be getting back to your cart?
是朗达叫我陪她坐的
Rhonda asked me to sit down.
我们明令禁止员工和会员过于亲密
There's a rule against staff fraternizing with members,
某人伸出脖子上的人头为你担保
and you wouldn't want to make trouble for whoever
推荐你来工作 你要安分
stuck their neck out to get you this job.
多伸伸脖子是好事
Oh, I recommend sticking your neck out.
那是唯一不动刀就能预防双下巴的方法
It's the only nonsurgical way to prevent champagne chin.
-说起来... -我去吧
- Speaking of which, um... - Oh, here. Let me get --
不不不 你坐 让他去
Oh, no, no, no, You sit. He's up.
给我也续一杯吧 杜克
You can top me off, too, Duke.
喝这个果蔬奶昔早餐最赞的是
I am loving this new smoothie kick.
我感觉我今天一天摄入的绿色蔬菜
I-I feel like I've had more green vegetables today
比我爸一辈子摄入得还多
than my dad's had in a lifetime.
我觉得你这新早餐最棒的地方
What I love about your smoothie kick
就是你总念叨个没完
is how much you talk about it.
如果你想损我至少想点有趣的梗
Okay, if you're gonna be mean, be funny.
把车往凸出的路面上推
Aim for the bumps.
卡尔喜欢偶尔颠一颠
Cal likes a bit of a bumpy ride
因为我直到孕期第四阶段还在开拖拉机
on account of I drove a tractor into my fourth trimester.
那声音总让我很不安
Oh, that sound makes me so nervous.
某个可怜的家庭就要天翻地覆了
Some poor family is about to have their life turned upside down.
好像拐到咱家那条街去了
they seem to be turning down our street.
我知道他们都是救火英雄
So, I-I know that they're-they're heroes and all,
但他们会帮我们打扫吗 还是我们自己来
but a-are they sweeping up or is that on us?
你知道吗 我们得一钉一铆
Okay, you know what? We're gonna have to totally rebuild,
彻底重建了
down to the studs.
我要抓狂了
I'm distraught.
是吗
Are ya?
我也不是一口咬定这火是小卡放的
I'm not saying Cam definitely set the fire.
犯人可能是任何一个
It could have been anyone who's spent years
多年来一直在找借口重建厨房的家伙
searching for a way to justify the remodel of our kitchen.
你不是真的在指控我故意放火
Are you actually accusing me of starting this fire
只为了能重建这个丑得要命的厨房吧
just so we could rebuild our hideous kitchen?
指控倒不至于
Uh, accusing, no.
不过你说"丑得要命的厨房"这种话时
but when you say things like "hideous kitchen,"
的确让我有所怀疑
it does make me wonder.
可能是这个引起了火灾
This could be the cause.
大多数厨房失火都是烤箱引起的
Most kitchen fires start in the oven.
我的天哪 我走时没关烤箱吗
Oh, my God, did-did I leave the oven on?
看来我们找到了热腾腾的罪魁祸"包"了
Well, it appears we found our smoking "bun."
她在这住了一夏天 估计是场硬仗
she's been here all summer, so this could be pretty rough.
还记得上次我们在她房间里发现了老鼠吗
Remember last time there was a rat in her room.
她是科学家 她说老鼠是用来做研究的
She's a scientist. She said it was part of a study.
亲爱的 老鼠是在麦片盒里发现的
Honey, it was in a cereal box.
来吧 超能英雄登场
Okay, time to be heroes.
换下脏床单 世界焕然一新
Change a bed sheet, change the world.
没错
That's right.
我都忘了你们两个要来
I completely forgot you guys were coming.
真不好意思
Oh, yeah, I'm so sorry.
我不知道你们要来 袜子没收好
I wasn't expecting you guys, so... sock.
那是我的旧单车吗
Oh, is that my old bike?
没错
Yep!
-为你翻新了 -太棒了
- Spruced it up for you. - That's great.
不过我刚刚买了辆新的
I actually just bought a new one, though.
你可以用那辆当备用零件
Guess you can use that one for parts.
瞧瞧这是什么 电动手套架
What do we have here? An electric mitten holder.
那是我刚建好的猜拳机器人
It's a rock-paper-scissors robot I just built.
什么
What?!
它的传感器能判断你要出什么
Its sensors anticipate your next move.
普通人才会中招
Maybe for civilians.
但我的敏捷手法是受过多年训练的
But I've been trained in the art of sleight of... hand!
终于
At last...
遇到对手了
a worthy opponent.
宝贝 我给你买了些不容易掉渣的零食
Honey, I got you some snacks that don't crumb up quite so easily.
我就给放在这个...
I'll just tuck them away in this...
已经都买好的零食柜里
fully-stocked snack cabinet.
别忘了纸巾和一次性餐盘
Don't forget the paper towels, the paper plates,
和卫生间的... 石头 不可思议
and the toilet -- Rock! How?!
看来你这里一切都井然有序
Seems like you're doing really, really well here.
那好 我得去机器人实验室了
Okay, well, I have to get to the robotics lab.
不过多谢你们过来看我
But, uh, thank you so much for visiting.
宝贝
Oh, honey.
感觉你表现得超棒
You seem to be doing so well.
洗发水
Shampoo.
我们真为你骄傲 艾丽克斯
We're so proud of you, Alex.
不只是因为你建了一个
And not just because you've built
几乎无法战胜的机器人 该死
a nearly unbeatable robot. Damn it!
-好吧 回见了 二位 -拜拜
- Okay, well, uh... bye, you guys. - Bye!
-拜拜 宝贝 -拜拜 宝贝
- Bye, honey. ?- Bye, honey.
她真的开始能独立了
She is really coming into her own, huh?
看我们把她教得多好
Look what we did.
我不确定这都是我们的功劳
I don't know if we can take all the credit.
她来这前不是这样子的
She wasn't like that before she got here.
是我们送她来的 亲爱的
You know what? We drove her here, honey.
是我们送她来的
We drove her here.
谁会需要两罐芥末
Two mustards. No one needs that.
这罐我拿走
We'll just take that one home.
那是她的新裙子
That is her new dress.
她买的时候可兴奋了
She was so excited about getting this.
她为什么要丢掉
Why would she throw it out?
你觉得有什么问题吗
Do you think something's going on?
可能 可能她打扫卫生 整理东西啊
Maybe -- Maybe all of the cleaning and the organizing
都是遭遇困难时的应对机制
is like a -- a coping mechanism.
对 从打扫整理与对自行车的冷漠回应...
Yeah, between that and the muted response to the bike...
我不知道 你觉得我们该找她谈谈吗
I don't know. You think we should talk to her?
我刚都不是在玩
I wasn't even playing.
啊哈 可恶
Boom! Damn it.
被枪抵着 我心中的前三名是
Gun to my head, my top three:
切达奶酪 瑞士硬奶酪 高达奶酪
cheddar, Swiss, gouda.
作为一个真被人拿枪抵着头过的人
As someone who has actually had a gun to her head,
他们才不会问你喜欢什么奶酪
cheese is not what they're going to ask about.
现在到饼干了
And now crackers.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
尴尬了
This is awkward.
我想改装个爷们天地
I need a boy cave.
别和我提布里奶酪
And don't get me started about brie.
不用担心
Oh, there's no risk of that.
当我没来过 明白吗
I'm not here, okay?
你给壁橱装上锁了吗
You put a lock on the closet?
我打算抓到圣诞老人后 把他关在里面
That's where I'm gonna put Santa Claus when I catch him.
给请他吃的饼干里加点安眠药
Sleeping pills in his cookies.
乔 你在和谁说话
Joe, who are you talking to?
天啊 我们俩小时前才把你送到学校
Oh, geez. We dropped you off at college two hours ago.
靠 海莉当时都比你待更久
My God, even Haley lasted longer.
我需要我的白噪声机
I needed my white noise machine.
还是你的棕色噪音妈啊
Or did you need your brown noise machine?
你这话我都替你自己感到被歧视
No, and I think I'm offended for you.
感觉像是你故意忘拿
It looks like you forgot that on purpose
好让你有借口回来安乐窝
so that you could come back to the nest.
哪有多"安乐"啊
Some "nest."
乔在鸠占鹊巢 你俩认为我是个小弱鸡
Joe is taking over my room, and you two think I'm a wimp.
不是小弱鸡 只是不爷们
Not wimp, just soft.
还非常 非常害怕
And very, very scared.
好了 你们能闭嘴了吗
Okay, can everyone please stop talking
这样我们完美的道别还能有点救
so we can salvage our perfect goodbye?
你上锁是干嘛
What's with the padlock?
我问你
Let me ask you something:
你想每天都过圣诞节吗
How would you like to have Christmas every day?
好了 我把我们所需要用的
Okay, I've put everything out here
厨房用品都放到这里了
from the kitchen that we're gonna need.
你知道吗 这会很有趣的
You know what? This is gonna be fun.
就好像露营
It's like camping!
有趣和好像露营并不会同时发生
Which is it -- fun or like camping?
我要去冲个澡
I'm gonna take a shower.
洗澡前先刷了这堆盘子
Can't take a shower without doing a load of dishes.
记得 糙的一边刷锅 软的一边手拿
And remember -- scratchy side pot, soft side you, okay?
小卡 这也太神经病了
Cam, this is crazy.
如果... 如果我想泡杯茶呢
What -- What if I wanted to make a cup of tea?
再简单不过了
Couldn't be simpler.
从餐具柜上拿茶壶
Grab a tea kettle from the credenza,
加水就从窗外接进来的水管加
warm it up on the hot plate with the water that you've used
然后放电炉上热就行了
from the hose that I snaked in through the window,
茶可以去我们壁炉架上找 然后茶杯就在...
browse the tea on the mantel, and then grab our tea cup --
茶杯在... 莉莉 先洗茶杯
Where -- Oh! Lily, do our tea cup first!
你们赶紧把走廊上的冰箱移走
Y'all need to move that 'fridgerator in your hall.
冰箱正好在小卡尔的婴儿床下方
It is straight under little Cal's crib,
冰箱的响声让他一直睡不着
and the noise is keeping him up...
这也怪了 他可是在屠宰场里怀上的啊
which is weird because he was conceived in a slaughterhouse.
-但我还以为... -赶紧移走
- But I thought... - ?Just move it!
你...
You...
他们找到起火的原因了吗
They figure out what started that fire?
嗯 他们认为起因在烤箱
Yeah, they think it was the oven.
不可能
Well, that's dumb.
咱们出去散步前我关了烤箱的
I turned the oven off 'fore we went on our walk.
-你关了吗 -对啊
- You did? - ?Yeah,
因为我是这儿唯一一个有责任心的人
'cause I'm the only responsible person around here.
靠 卡尔又从沙发上滚下来了
Dang it! Cal rolled off the sofa again!
天啊 不 不 不
Oh, God. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
有那么一丝可能 凶手绝对是我
There's a small chance I definitely started the fire.
-米奇尔 -奶昔有点稠
- Mitchell? - ?My smoothie was a little thick.
这样还挺方便啊
This is convenient. Huh?
我要给你看点东西
There's something I need to show you.
是什么 来这儿 来这儿看
Yeah. What is it? Over here. Over here. Let's look.
是我梦想厨房的展望板
It's a vision board for my dream kitchen
我一直藏在你的健身服后面
I've been hiding behind your workout clothes. ?Ah.
我觉得我不小心 成心地
I-I-I think I accidentally, on purpose,
下意识地 故意地烧了咱们的厨房
subconsciously, willfully, burned our kitchen down.
我不... 这很难说吧
Okay. I-I don't -- I don't know about that.
不 面对现实吧
Um -- ?No. Let's face it.
就像德鲁·巴里摩尔 我是个可爱的纵火犯
Like Drew Barrymore, I'm an adorable fire starter.
这就是为什么我们家胶布总是没了吗
Is this why we never have any tape?
对 我是个危险人物 所以应该由你
Yes. I'm a menace, which is why you deserve
全权负责这次改造
to be in charge of this entire remodel.
你说了算
Anything you say goes.
小卡 你听完这话感觉会好点的...
Cam, you're about to feel a lot better because
我觉得这烤面包机还行
I don't hate this toaster,
我觉得我能找到位子摆放
and I think I can find a place for it.
太好了
That's great.
我能习惯这种生活
I could get used to this.
我已经习惯了 所以在我亡夫特么的钱
I have, which is why I need to snag another meal ticket
用完之前 我得另找一张饭票
before my late husband's fracking money runs out.
没事 你可以在我面前直接骂脏话
It's okay. You can swear in front of me.
那边那个 在打网球的男人怎么样
How about that guy over there, playing tennis?
他体态挺好
He's in good shape.
对吧
Right?
不 这个不行
No, that's a negative.
我要那种拿网球当助行器缓冲的老头
I want my guys' tennis balls to be at the end of their walkers.
好吧... 那...
Okay. Uh, how about, uh...
那个怎么样
that guy over there?
我想那是个被人丢弃的高尔夫球袋
I think that's just an abandoned golf bag,
不过你开始理解我的意思了
but you're starting to get me.
你想当我的私人助理吗
You know, would you like to be my personal assistant?
平时要我做什么
What would I have to do?
除了帮我找个新老公
Apart from helping me find a new husband,
大部分时间就是玩一玩 喝喝酒 去派对浪一浪
it's mostly... hanging out, drinking, going to parties.
我是完美人选
I am perfect for this.
有太多人可以为我举荐
I have so many references.
好的
Okay, uh...
那个在玩推圆盘游戏的怎么样 沃里斯先生
what about that guy going to play shuffleboard -- Mr. Voorhees?
他比我以前的那些老公年轻
Uh, he's a little younger than I normally do.
给你点参考 他向来
If it helps, he always orders
只点那些适合心脏病人的鸡尾酒
from the HeartSmart side of my cocktail menu.
你很在行啊
You are good at this.
让我去给他的心脏起搏器添加点压力
Let me go give that pacemaker something to do.
海莉 你应该在高尔夫球场端酒
Haley, you're supposed to be on the course serving drinks.
我很忙 卢克
I'm busy, Luke.
我们不能让客人清醒着打球
We can't have people golfing sober.
他们会发现那就是在浪费时间
They'll realize it's a waste of time.
我不太想再继续当球车女郎了
I'm not even sure I want to be a cart girl anymore.
罗娜要我当她的私人助理
Rhonda asked me to be her personal assistant.
我知道这不算什么迷人的职业
I know this isn't the most glamorous job,
但是 这份工作提供的未来
but...it offers more of a future
比给色诱老男人换钱的女人当助理靠谱多了
than being an assistant to some gold digger.
喂
Hello?
好消息 沃里斯有个朋友
Hey, good news -- Voorhees has a friend,
他想带我们飞去旧金山玩 就今晚
and he wants to fly us all to San Francisco tonight.
这里能带你走向阳光大道
You're on a good path here.
你在赚钱 有很好的晋升机会
You're making money. There's opportunity for advancement.
这趟旅行肯定很棒
It's gonna be great.
最豪华的酒店 最高档的餐厅 全天候护理
Best hotels, best restaurants, round-the-clock nursing.
你比她强 海莉
You're better than her, Haley.
-算我一个 -很好
- I'm in. - ?Oh, good.
车子五点钟来接我们 也就是吃完晚饭后
The car will pick us up at 5:00, right after dinner.
我干嘛跟你浪费唇舌
Why do I even bother?
我跟你说的话你都右耳朵进
It's like what I say to you goes in one ear...
左耳朵出了
out the other.
不知道你是怎么样 我反正准备好独立生活了
Don't know about you, but I am ready to live on my own.
的确 照顾我的父母是艰巨的责任
Yep, it was a big responsibility taking care of my parents,
但是我也交棒给了一个可靠的人
but I left a good man on the job.
又来
Come on.
歌洛莉亚 你又把电视弄坏了 我看不了节目了
Gloria, you messed up the TV, and now I can't watch my program!
记得你让我在你像个老年人时提醒你吗
Remember how you told me to say something when you sound old?
没事了 我弄好了
Ah, never mind. I fixed it.
瞧瞧这些美丽的花儿
Look at those beautiful flowers.
哪儿来的
Where did they come from?
不知道
Not a clue.
你弄的吧
Aww, you.
乔
Joe?
你在做什么
What are you making?
纸上写了 这是一种古老的饮料
According to this, an ancient beverage
苏丹王和流氓们都喜欢喝
enjoyed by sultans and scoundrels.
"捡报纸 做咖啡
"Bring in the paper, make coffee...
捡起杰的脏袜子"
pick up Jay's dirty socks."
你怎么在做这些事
Why are you doing all this?
曼尼说以后这些都靠我了
Manny says it's my job now.
一直以来都是曼尼在做这些事吗
Manny was doing all these things?
我还很高兴你终于开始自己捡起脏袜子了
And I was so happy that you were picking up after yourself.
我上世纪70年代起就没捡过了
I haven't picked up socks since the '70s.
这么久以来 我们都以为是我们在照顾曼尼
Huh, all this time, we're thinking we're coddling Manny,
其实是他在照顾我们
and Manny was coddling us.
我要打给他夸他是个多么好的孩子
I am going to call him and tell him what a good boy he is.
歌洛莉亚 要是你这么激动地打给他
Gloria, if you call him all worked up,
他肯定两秒钟就开哭了
he'll be in tears in two seconds.
他只想洒脱地离开
What he wanted was a nice clean exit.
我们得坚持住让他完成心愿
We have to stay strong and give him that.
好吧
I guess.
我们找点事儿分散下注意力
I say we distract ourselves.
我去俱乐部 讲点荤段子
I'll go to the club, crack some inappropriate jokes,
给宇航员排个名 在桑拿池里打个盹
rank the astronauts, fall asleep in the sauna.
好 玩得开心点
Okay. Have fun.
我跟乔去逛街
I'll go shopping with Joe.
买玩具吗
For toys?
不 买鞋子
No. For shoes.
现在难过的人是我 不是你
I'm the one that is sad, not you.
太酷了
How cool.
别分心 菲尔
Just stay focused, Phil.
亲爱的 亲爱的
Honey, honey.
不管这些机器人给人的感觉多真实
No matter how realistic these robots get,
我还是会永远爱你
I'm always going to love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
她在这儿呢
There she is.
-看这里 -亲爱的
- Hi! Hi! - Honey!
抱歉 那是无尘工作间
Uh, excuse me, that's a clean room.
你们必须穿上无尘服 在空气浴尘室
You can't go in there without putting on a sterile suit
去除所有可能的污染物后才能进入
and taking an air shower to remove all possible contaminants.
真的很像真人啊
They really are lifelike.
我觉得还是你去跟她说吧
I think you should handle this.
我不... 我不想让我们女儿
I don't, uh... I don't want to overwhelm
太... 太难以承受
our -- our daughter.
打到你啦
Yes.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
这是设计来做心血管外科手术的机械手
That was designed to perform cardiovascular surgery.
真... 真是对不起
I'm -- I'm -- I'm so sorry.
那请问有趣的机器人是在哪里
Um....where -- where are the fun ones?
感觉还不差
I didn't hate that.
妈 你来这里做什么
Mom, what are you doing here?
是这样的 我跟你爸爸本来要出你房间了
Okay, well, your father and I were leaving your room,
结果我们发现到
and we noticed, oh,
你把你很爱的那件可爱裙子给扔了
you'd thrown out that cute dress you love so much.
我就想"为什么 她为什么会丢掉"
And I thought to myself, "Why? Why would she do that?"
我就想 也许... 也许是你穿给某个男生看
And I thought maybe -- maybe you tried to wear it for a boy,
想给他留下好感 结果事与愿违 心里难受
to impress him, and it didn't go well, and it made you feel bad.
也可能只是我不喜欢那件裙子啊
Or, maybe I just didn't like the dress.
或是我猜的那样
Or my thing.
没事 你教训我是对的
No, it's my fault you yelled at me.
你们这里的孩子得承受超大的压力
You kids here are under extreme pressure.
超大压力
Extreme pressure.
你个傻子
You fool.
-老爸 -艾丽克斯
- Dad... - Alex.
我跟你说过有关一位男拉拉队员
Did I ever tell you about a certain male cheerleader
在做空中翻转动作时翻转过度的事吗
who over-rotated during a Flying Half Toby?
他最后一跛一跛地走回宿舍
He limped his way back to his dorm room
把他最爱的服装给扔了
and threw out his favorite outfit,
因为他这个失败者不配穿那件哈伦裤
because harem pants are for winners.
两位 我真没事
Guys, I'm fine!
你们为什么一直要让我觉得我有事
Why do you keep trying to solve a problem that doesn't exist?
不知道 或许我们只是还想被你需要
I don't know. Maybe we just want to feel like you still need us.
但看看你 你才不需要我们呢
But look at you. You don't need anything.
这样很棒啊
Which is terrific.
你就是我们无所不能的超级女儿
You're our little superstar who can do anything.
不是 我真不是
I'm not. I'm not.
我完全完全不觉得是这样
I totally, totally, totally don't feel that way.
快闭嘴
Shut up!
是有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
好吧 行 如果你们非要知道
Okay, fine. if you really must know,
我在这里一直感觉融入不了大家
I've been kind of feeling like an outsider here.
后来我发现我可能有点太爱出风头
It's come to my attention that I may be a bit of a show-off.
在我的高等混沌数学课上有道题
There's a proof in my advanced mathematical chaos class.
在白板上已经一整年了 都没人能解
It's been on the board all year. No one could solve it.
直到某天晚上 我一个灵光一闪
Until one night in bed, it just came to me.
我当然得为那一刻穿上我最好看的裙子
And of course I had to put on my best dress for my big moment.
解完收工
Class dismissed.
我再也不想看到那件白痴裙子了
I just never want to see that stupid dress again.
宝贝 人们永远都会被你的才智所震慑
Honey, people are always gonna be intimidated by your intellect.
或许你也该对他们露出一些脆弱之处了
Maybe it's time you showed them some of your vulnerability.
他们怎么可能没看过
How have they not seen it?
我从小到大都是个书呆死宅
I've been an awkward nerd my whole life.
但在这里你不是啊
Everywhere but here.
亲爱的 在这里...
Sweetheart, here...
你就是海莉
you're Haley.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我知道很烂 但这只是半成品
I know it's stinks! It's a work in progress.
不是的 你这个掉了而已
No, you, uh... just dropped this.
而且... 其实你没什么好担心的啊
And, actually, you've got nothing to worry about.
我的进度比你落后多了
You're way further along than I am.
我都有点抓狂了
I'm kind of freaking out.
真的吗
Really?
我做了一个猜拳机器人 而且做得超烂
I built a rock-paper-scissors robot, and it sucks.
-跟它猜10次我能赢8次 -真的吗
- I beat it 8 out of 10 times. - What?
如果你现在不是很忙
Hey, if you're not too busy right now,
你愿意帮忙我弄一下我的吗
do you think maybe you'd want to help me with mine a little bit?
可以啊
Sure.
同志 干得好
Nice work, partner.
药到病除
That was a clinic.
咱俩教孩子真是强到极限了
Yeah, we are parenting at the highest possible level.
强到极限
Highest possible level.
你们俩傻子
You fools!
我按你要求打给酒店了
So, I called the hotel like you asked.
小吧台补满了你要求的酒
Mini-bar's stocked with rose and Ensure.
然后取消掉一个人的预定了
And I canceled the one reservation.
是谁不来了
Who's not coming?
这件事嘛 我们得谈谈
About that, uh, we need to talk.
好
Okay.
车门锁上了
It's locked.
沃里斯先生在听说
Mr. Voorhees was a little too excited
那个球车女郎也来的时候 特别激动
to hear that the cart girl was tagging along.
抱歉 但我不想冒
I'm sorry, but I can't risk being upstaged
被性感30岁辣妹给抢风头的风险
by a hot-to-trot 30-year-old.
有点乱四舍五入了啊
Kind of rounded up there.
所以 我就这么不再是你的助理了吗
So, I'm just out as your assistant, like that?
我内心比表露出来的难过多了
It's harder on me than it looks.
我感觉真的...
I feel really...
要说就说吧
Go ahead.
第七洞有四人组感觉很口渴
There's a foursome on the seventh green that looks thirsty.
谢谢你 老板
Thanks, boss.
卢克 你绝对不会后悔第一次请了球车男郎
Luke! Luke, you will not regret hiring your first male cart girl.
我之前没说 但我之前一直在人生谷底
I didn't mention, but I've been in a really dark place.
不介意的话 我可以不围这个丝巾吗
Hey, do you mind if I ditch the kerchief?
这个嘛
Yeah...
可能需要你交还你的皮带跟鞋带
might want to hand over your belt and shoelaces, too.
我们边走边聊吧 鲁本
Take a walk with me, Reuben.
你家冻芒果快没了 记得加在你的购物清单上
You're low on frozen mangoes. Put it on your list.
对了 再帮我带一盒卫生棉条
Oh, and get me a box of lady sticks.
你在做什么
What -- What -- What are you making?
我在做你们的一种娘基[水果]沙冰
I'm making one of your fruit smoothies.
-小帕 -好啦 我重说
- Oh, Pam. - ?All right,
我在做一个你们男同性恋者的沙冰
I'm making one of your homosexual smoothies.
-怎么搞的 -我天
- What the hell? ?- Oh, my gosh.
妈呀
Oh, my gosh! Okay.
去拿水管 快去拿水管 在窗户那边
Get the hose! Get the hose! It's in the window!
快点 米奇
Oh, Mitchell! hurry!
我敢打赌这就是厨房起火的原因
I bet that's what started the fire.
这怎么可能
Well, h-how can it be
这可是它第一次这么冒火花啊
when that's the first time it's sparked ever?
是啊 应该是烤箱造成的
Yeah, it was the oven.
我出门前把烤箱关了 我跟米奇尔说过了
I turned that off. I told Mitchell.
-她说过吗 -你跟我说过吗
- She did? ?- Did you? I --
如果你说过我应该有印象啊
See, I feel like I'd remember that.
厨房你烧的 结果你让我背锅吗
You let me think I burned down the kitchen when you did?
不然改造厨房的事我一点话语权都没有
It was the only way for me to get a say in the remodel.
要不要这么夸张啊
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
我也有让你挑选东西啊
I let you pick things.
是吗 这里你说出一件是我挑的东西
Really? Name one thing in this room that was my idea.
就一件 一件 说一件是吗
Oh, just one -- one thing? One thing. Mm-hmm.
可以 我看看
Okay, well, fine.
毛毯 这个毛毯怎么说
how -- how about the blanket?
你说这个毛毯会让你想起你以前
Yeah, because you said it reminded you of the blanket
在爷爷奶奶家里躺的那毯子
you used to lay on at your grandparents' house
那时你一边吃着焦糖玉米 一边看电视
and eat your caramel corn when you watched
看着玛丽·卢·雷顿为美国夺下奥运体操金牌
Mary Lou Retton vault her way into America's heart.
你在说些什么乱七八糟的
What are you talking about?
你该不会觉得可以强行将回忆植入我脑中
Are -- Are you seriously trying to incept a memory in my mind
我就会真觉得是我自己挑的吧
to make me believe that I chose that blanket?
就像你让我觉得厨房是我烧的那样吗
Oh, kind of like you made me think I burned down our kitchen?
好了
Okay, whoa.
为什么我们要这样折磨对方
Why do we keep doing this to each other?
对啊 我们已经残缺到连诚实都做不到了吗
I know. Are we so broken that we can't even be honest?
说到残缺 买个新的搅拌机如何
Speaking of broken, how about a new blender?
麻利麻利
Chop chop --
是搅拌机品牌 也是让你们麻利点
That is both the brand and when I want it!
我想到了 我有个理论
okay. I have a theory...
可以让我们原谅自己
...uh, that lets us both off the hook.
我很乐意支持
I'm inclined to be on board.
我们都同意你的姐姐
Um, we both can agree that your sister
-有点倚强凌弱 -是的
- can be a bit of a bully. - Yes.
我确定你成长过程中
I'm sure growing up,
想达到目的 就必须使出点小手段
the only way to get your way was to be manipulative.
在你成长过程中 也同样受到
It might also be said you grew up oppressed
史上最恶的恶魔之一欺压
by one of history's great monsters --
也就是你姐 克莱尔
your sister, Claire.
正是如此
Exactly.
我们才不糟糕
We're not terrible.
-是她们 -是她们
- They are. - They are.
杰
Jay?
我在你床下发现了这个
I found this under your bed.
我想你可能会需要用到它
I figured you might be able to use it.
毕竟 你应该也不想成为
I mean, you don't want to be
一所艺术学校里唯一没有贝雷帽的学生吧
the only kid in art school without a beret.
谢谢 既然你已经来了
Thanks. Since you're here,
你想见一见我的新室友吗
you want to meet my new roommate?
他的东西不在了
His stuff's gone.
有人在吗
Knock, knock!
杰 你在这里干嘛
Hi, Jay, what are you doing here?
你不是说你要去俱乐部吗
I thought you were at the club.
你不是说你要去买鞋吗
You said you were going shopping.
是啊
I was...
但后来我逛街时看到了这个小枕头
but then I saw this little pillow.
看 "闻鸡起舞 大杀四方 反复循环"
Look -- "Wake Up, Kick Ass, Repeat."
是不是特别适合曼尼
Isn't it so Manny?
谢了 妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
好了 帽子已经送到了 我就先撤了
So, you got your hat, so I'm gonna...
对了 如果我之前没有说过
Look, if I didn't say it...
你来这里念书 很了不起
it's a big deal, you going here.
干得不错
Good job.
如果我之前没有说过
Well, if I didn't say it,
没有你的付出 我也做不到
I-I couldn't have done it without you.
我们这是干嘛
What are we doing?
我们可以拥抱的 我们是一家人啊
We can hug. We're family. ?Yeah.
我们真的是
We are, you know.
我们真的是一家人
We're family.
我会努力让你们感到骄傲的
I'll try to make you proud.
你已经做到了
You already have.
让我也抱一个
Let me in here!
谢谢你一直默默照顾着我们
Thank you for taking good care of us.
你对你爱的人就是会这么付出
Well, that's what you do for the people you love.
你爱的人也爱你
They love you, too!
可恶
Damn it!
-可恶 -认输并不可耻
- Damn it. - There's no shame in admitting defeat.
你不懂啦 他要累了
You don't understand. He's getting tired.
这才是重点 他才不会累 他是个机器
He's not tired. That's the point. He's a Machine.
你能不能就对我有信心一次啊
Just once, would you believe in me?!
你是我老婆 你不是应该当我人生的基"石"吗
As my wife, aren't you supposed to be my rock?
靠
Damn it!
每个妈妈都会教育小孩 不可以
What does every mother tell their kid not to
拿着... 布[剪刀]跑
run with? Paper!
我去
Damn it!
我的手开始酸了
My hand is getting tired.
对不起啊 小伙子 怎么不早点说
Oh, I'm so sorry, buddy. Why didn't you say so?
来击个拳
Fist bump.
哈 垃圾
Ha! Loser.
-不 -还是冠军
- No. - And still champion!